5/417, Echampatti, Rayakottai, Krishnagiri, Tamil Nadu-635116 + 91-8838357016 rajsram.github.io RajeshSivasankaran@outlook.com

RAJESH SIVASANKARAN

PROFILE SUMMARY

Having **6+ years** of experience in analysis, design, development of windows, web, and mobile-based application.

Experience in development of .Net framework and Core, Angular, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SQL, and Azure.

Self-learning of React, Node JS and python.

Effective in working independently and collaboratively in teams.

Code managing with TFS, Azure DevOps and GitHub.

A self-motivated person with the ability to learn new technologies and adapt to new environment.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Client Side	HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Typescript, Angular 2+ and React
Server Side	C#.Net, ASP.Net MVC, .Net Core, Web API, Node Js
Databases	MSSQL, MySQL.
Cloud	Azure, App Service, VM, Blob and Key vault
Mobile	Ionic, Android and IOS (customize)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Senior Software Engineer, Carl Zeiss India, Bengaluru, Karnataka.

zeiss.com

Jul 2018 - Till

Software Engineer, Mindteck (India) Limited (Zeiss India),

Bengaluru, Karnataka.

mindteck.com

Aug 2017 – Jul 2018

Software Engineer, Cogwave software Technologies Pvt. Ltd, Bengaluru, Karnataka.

cogwave.in

Jun 2016 - Jul 2017

Software Engineer, Sivasakthi Software Services Pvt. Ltd, Coimbatore, Tamilnadu.

sivasakthisoft.com

Jul 2014 - May 2016

EDUCATION Master of Computer Applications (MCA)

2011 - 2014

Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA)

2008 - 2014

Higher Secondary Certificate (HSC)

2006 - 2008

Secondary School Leaving Certificate (SSLC)

2006

PROJECTS

Project Name	Online Update System
Duration	Jul 2018 – Till
Team size	7
Technologies	.Net Core WebAPI, HTML, CSS, Angular 6 and Azure
Role	Developer & Minor release lead
Responsibilities	UI from scratch, Web API, Database and Collaborate with global team

Project Name	Primus
Duration	Aug 2017 – Jul 2018
Team size	5
Technologies	ASP.Net MVC & WebApi2 HTML & CSS & JavaScript & jQuery Angular 5
Role	Developer
Responsibilities	UI & Service & Bug Fixing Coordinated all updates with TFS

Project Name	HMS (Hotel Management System)
Duration	Apr 2017 – Jul 2017
Team size	2
Technologies	ASP.Net MVC 5 & WebApi2 Dapper ORM & Autofac Kendo UI HTML & CSS & JavaScript & jQuery MS SQL Server
Role	Full Stack Developer

Responsibilities	UI & Service & Bug Fixing & Stored Procedures	
	Coordinated all updates with TFS	

Project Name	eKOT – POS
Duration	Mar 2017 – Apr 2017
Team size	2
Technologies	ASP.Net WebAPI 2 Dapper ORM & Autofac & Fluent Validation Angular 2 & Ionic 2 & TypeScript & Cordova MS SQL Server
Role	Full Stack Developer
Responsibilities	Design UI & Service & Bug Fixing Coordinated all updates with TFS

Project Name	House Keeping - HMS (Hotel Management System)
Duration	Feb 2017 – Mar 2017
Team size	3
Technologies	ASP.Net MVC 5 & WebApi2 Dapper ORM & Autofac HTML & Material CSS & JavaScript & jQuery MS SQL Server
Role	Full Stack Developer
Responsibilities	UI & Server Code & Bug Fixing & Stored Procedures Coordinated all updates with TFS

Project Name	Online Reporting - HMS (Hotel Management System)
Duration	Jan 2017 – Feb 2017
Team size	3
Technologies	ASP.Net MVC 5 & WebApi2 Dapper ORM & Autofac HTML & Material CSS & JavaScript & jQuery MS SQL Server
Role	Full Stack Developer
Responsibilities	UI & Code Development & Bug Fixing Stored Procedures Coordinated all updates with TFS

Project Name	HIS (Hospital Information System)
Duration	Jul 2016 – Dec 2016
Team size	5

Technologies	ASP.Net WebApi2 Dapper ORM & Autofac & Fluent Validation Angular 2 & TypeScript & HTML & Bootstrap CSS MS SQL Server
Role	Full Stack Developer
Responsibilities	UI & Code Development & Bug Fixing Stored Procedures Coordinated all updates with TFS

Project Name	SS KOT
Duration	Feb 2016 – May 2016
Team size	2
Technologies	ASP.Net WebApi2 & Entity Framework ORM HTML & CSS & JavaScript & Cordova MS SQL Server
Role	Full Stack Developer
Responsibilities	UI & Code Development & Bug Fixing

Project Name	Chit Fund Management
Duration	Jul 2015 – Feb 2016
Team size	4
Technologies	ASP.Net MVC & Entity Framework ORM & Dev Express HTML & CSS & JavaScript & jQuery MS SQL Server
Role	Full Stack Developer
Responsibilities	Database and Coding & Code Review Reporting with Team Leader Bug Fixing and Coordinated all updates

Project Name	Finance/Accounts Maintenance
Duration	Jul 2014 – Jul 2015
Team size	5
Technologies	VB.Net
	Dev Express
	MS SQL & MySQL
Role	Developer
Roles &	Reporting with Team Leader
Responsibilities	Bug Fixing
	Coordinated all updates
	Custom module development
	Customer Support